They landed and one of the aliens
even appeared as a
shadowy shape in a
shopping center in Miami, but dozens of
police officers were called in and even
more videos are circulating on the Internet that are
supposed to show that an alien in
Miami is circulating on the Internet one way or another
I also felt that a lot of you wrote to me
in every second comment
about what the hell is
going on in Miami or what will play a very important role on January 1st
on New Year's Day,
what's
going on there, let's take a closer look at it
today very precisely what is
behind this really huge
police operation and what the
many videos are all about and
a lot of strange videos are
currently coming to light that are
supposed to show these shadowy alien creatures,
as always right after the
intro,
like you First of all, see a small
disclaimer, I'm currently on
vacation in Holland for 6 days, I
had already informed most of you about it,
so today it's a little more casual
and with a completely different background.
Forgive me for the poor
audio quality and the quality of the picture, which is
really very, very good here Everything is dark and
freezing cold but what is it about? You
will have probably already heard it somewhere
on the many, many channels that
report on it. 60 police cars, a
huge contingent of
police forces because of an
alleged shadowy creature that is very blurry,
alien shadow
creature or whatever has been mentioned
in the last few days but what's
behind it? Let's first look
at the pictures that show this
unusual, I would say
unusual picture, which
even major American media
outlets are reporting on
A lot of
social media users have
aroused the suspicion that it's more
than just what the official
statement from the police is, namely
teenagers who were having a little fight, it
wouldn't be, but it would be
this huge police presence would only have
been there because of this very
shadowy, blurred creature that
you can see in the pictures of the yes, I assume
it's a police helicopter, we
have a
bird's eye view here, yes and as is
often the case, this video went viral on social media
There
they claim to have
identified a certain scene in the footage that took place exactly in
front of the shopping center in Miami
on Monday, January 1st, namely
this very difficult to
recognize, very shadowy, very
blurry figure that, according to
theories,
is foot It is supposed to be 10 feet tall,
which would be the equivalent of almost 3 m and
yes, on social media this is
described by some as a shadow creature and by others as an extraterrestrial creature, which
was the actual trigger for the operation,
this huge police force and
not these few Teenagers who
had a bit of a fight,
what's interesting is that there were more and
more videos on Ex. In the past, it wasn't
Telegram but Twitter. Elon Musk has
renamed it Ex and not only are more and
more witnesses appearing there who actually
testify to them Yes, they saw this 3 m tall
alien in front of them, it
always disappeared and then
reappeared, but there is actually
also short clips of footage that they
then uploaded. I'll
also play a few of them for you. You can see
one walking on four legs
spider-like creature you see UFOs in the
sky of Miami it's supposed to be I have to
tell you very clearly that I know
these videos and they are from before
January 1st, they even come from the last
2 3 4 years, I have seen these exact
videos before and Especially
this alleged UFO, these
luminous dots, a really
bright object in the clouds, it definitely does
n't come from Miami because
I showed you that a few years ago,
so we should definitely be
very, very careful with
it and just as careful We are
actually with these very, very
blurry images because what we
see could be anything and there is
a reason for this very high or
strong police presence that the
strength of the police deployment of the
police forces can be
explained relatively well and I believe that
too According to the official statements from the
responsible police authority, these
young people, this fight between the
teenagers, young people all around 15 or
16 years old, they had
fireworks with them, which of course
fits with January 1st, New Year's Day, and they are said to have
played around with firecrackers and the corresponding firecrackers on each other
and of course it bangs
and some of the passers-by
in the shopping center
actually thought that someone was running amok,
someone had
a machine gun with them
and it was actually running amok and
banging and what should I do if I
a passer-by is in a panic, I call
the police and the police will
certainly send dozens of people
there first, e.g. 60
police cars to secure the area
first because it could
always happen and we have to
remember that it is the USA there yes
unfortunately unfortunately unfortunately something like this is actually
the order of the day almost so the
whole thing makes sense to me that we do
n't see an alien shadow creature in these blurry shots
but actually just
something that was perhaps misinterpreted
and all the other videos and the
witness statements on Twitter
Nowadays, unfortunately, I would
n't take them too seriously, but as I
said, it's
much weirder for me that
something like that and the media has so
all the major American media have
reported on it right now
Feint that
such a feint goes viral and
goes through the media instead of really the
interesting news that will be
published again and again by credible witnesses in 2024 and we only have the beginning of the year, as
I said, I have already told you about Daniel Sheen,
and David Grush has also at the
very beginning of the year there was a kind of
new documentary and revelations
and and and and then there's
this completely inflated thing about aliens
in
Miami, shadow creatures in Miami. I do
n't really know what to
think of it, but this incident
goes so viral and reaches many, many more
people than the actual
good topics, the credible topics, yes, what
else can I say about that, that's how the
internet is, that's how the media is, what a
very short time when there is video material about it
where you can only guess something can it
be pushed up endlessly and the
really true cases are
a little too much for me that's it
for today from vacation it was
on my heart
to inform you about it and give you
my opinion on this yes As I just
said, very inflated viral
video of an alien creature in
Miami, yes I'll let you know my opinion, we'll
see each other again
in the next few days with a little video
from my vacation, I'll be
there until Friday, stay safe and keep my
eyes open until then and
until the next video like that